A Guide to the Russell Sage Foundation records FA015
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Russell Sage Foundation records, 1974-2002; 2; 120 Cubic Feet 252 document boxes.
  - Grants, 1974-2002; 3; 52.5 Cubic Feet
    - Tomasi, Lydio, Presidential Grant, Children of Immigrants, 889.402, Attachment File, 1992-1994 (Box 173, Folder 1227A)
    - Torrey, Barbara, Workshop on Social Science Infrastructure, 97-97-13, 1997-1999 (Box 173, Folder 1228)
    - Torrey, Barbara, Workshop on Social Science Infrastructure, 97-97-13, 1997-1999 (Box 173, Folder 1228A)
    - Traugott, Michael W. and Warren E. Miller (Warren I. Mitofsky), CBS News/National Election Study Surveys: Coordinated Data Colelction in 1980, 1979-1982 (Box 173, Folder 1229)
    - Treas, Judith and Ramon Torrecilha, 1990 Census Project, The Older Population: Demographic, Social and Economic Trends, 90-81-07, 1991-1996 (Box 174, Folder 1230)
    - Treas, Judith and Ramon Torrecilha, 1990 Census Project, The Older Population: Demographic, Social and Economic Trends, 90-81-07, 1991-1996 (Box 174, Folder 1230A)
    - Tucker, M. Belinda, Presidential Grant, Conference: The Decline of Marriage Among American Blacks: Causes, Consequences and Polilcy Implications, 998.921, 1989-1996 (Box 174, Folder 1231)
    - Tucker, M. Belinda, Presidential Grant, Conference: The Decline of Marriage Among American Blacks: Causes, Consequences and Polilcy Implications, 998.921, Attachment File, 1989 (Box 174, Folder 1232)
    - Turner, Charles F., Presidential Grant, Improving Subjective and Objective Measurements Used in Epidemiologic Surveys of Plumonary Disorders, 1985-1991 (Box 174, Folder 1233)
    - Tyack, David B. and Elisabeth Hansot, How Gender Has Shaped Public Education: A Historical Analysis, 1982-1989 (Box 174, Folder 1234)
    - Valian, Virginia, Presidential Grant, Women and Achievement, 91-87-07, 1990-1998 (Box 174, Folder 1235)
    - Valian, Virginia, Presidential Grant, Women and Achievement, 91-87-07, Attachment File, 1993 (Box 175, Folder 1236)
    - Wakeman, Frederick, Social Science Research Council, Research on the Effects of Community and Neighborhood Conditions on Family Processes and Individual Development in Areas of Concentrated Urban Poverty, 978.708, 1987-1996 (Box 175, Folder 1237)
    - Wakeman, Frederick, Social Science Research Council, Research on the Effects of Community and Neighborhood Conditions on Family Processes and Individual Development in Areas of Concentrated Urban Poverty, 978.708, 1987-1996 (Box 175, Folder 1237A)
    - Wakeman, Frederick, Social Science Research Council, Research on the Effects of Community and Neighborhood Conditions on Family Processes and Individual Development in Areas of Concentrated Urban Poverty, 978.708, Attachment File, 1989 (Box 175, Folder 1238)
    - Wald, Michael S., Research on Children in Contemporary Society, 99-89-34, 1988-1997 (Box 175, Folder 1239)
    - Wald, Michael S., Research on Children in Contemporary Society, 99-89-34, 1988-1997 (Box 175, Folder 1239A)
    - Waldinger, Roger and Mehdi Bozorgmehr, Ethnic Los Angeles, 889.304, 1992-1997 (Box 175, Folder 1240)
    - Waldinger, Roger and Mehdi Bozorgmehr, Ethnic Los Angeles, 889.304, 1992-1997 (Box 175, Folder 1240A)
      Contains time sensitive material --- open in 2016
    - Waters, Mary, Racial and Ethnic Identity of Black Immigrants to the United States, 88-91-02, 1989-2000 (Box 175, Folder 1241)
    - Waters, Mary, Racial and Ethnic Identity of Black Immigrants to the United States, 88-91-02, 1989-2000 (Box 175, Folder 1241A)
    - Waters, Mary, Racial and Ethnic Identity of Black Immigrants to the United States, 88-91-02, Attachment File, 1991-1995 (Box 176, Folder 1242)
    - Weber, Roberto, Game Theory, 98-97-05, 1996-1998 (Box 176, Folder 1243)
    - Weber, Roberto, Game Theory, 98-97-05, 1996-1988 (Box 176, Folder 1243A)
    - Weir, Margaret M., The American Politic Process (The Gridlock Initiative), 97-93-03, 1993 (Box 176, Folder 1244)
    - Weir, Margaret M., In Support of a Working Group to Design a Program of Research Analyzing Social Policy Initiatives, 979.404, 1993-1996 (Box 176, Folder 1245)
    - Weir, Margaret M., In Support of a Working Group to Design a Program of Research Analyzing Social Policy Initiatives, 979.404, 1993-1996 (Box 176, Folder 1245A)
    - Weir, Margaret M., Politics of Social Policy: Planning Meeting, 869.401, 1994-1996 (Box 176, Folder 1246)
    - Weir, Margaret M., Politics of Social Policy: Planning Meeting, 869.401, 1994-1996 (Box 176, Folder 1246A)
    - Weir, Margaret M. and R. Kent Weaver, Politics of Social Policy in the Clinton Administration, 86-97-09, 1994-1998 (Box 176, Folder 1247)
    - Weir, Margaret M. and R. Kent Weaver, Politics of Social Policy in the Clinton Administration, 86-97-09, 1994-1998 (Box 176, Folder 1247A)
    - Weir, Margaret M. and R. Kent Weaver, Politics of Social Policy in the Clinton Administration, 86-97-09, Attachement File, 1994-1995 & 1998 (Box 176, Folder 1248)
    - Weir, Margaret M. and R. Kent Weaver, Politics of Social Policy in the Clinton Administration, 86-97-09, Attachement File, 1994-1995 & 1998 (Box 177, Folder 1248A)
    - Westin, Alan F., Due Process Mechanisms in American Industry, 1980-1988 (Box 177, Folder 1249)
    - Westin, Alan F., Presidential Grant, Due Process for Employees in the Corporate Workplace, 1981-1987 (Box 177, Folder 1250)
    - Wetzel, James, 1990 Census Project, Trends in Labor Force Participation, Unemployment and Earnings, 909.301, 1991-1996 (Box 177, Folder 1251)
    - Wetzel, James, 1990 Census Project, Trends in Labor Force Participation, Unemployment and Earnings, 909.301, 1991-1996 (Box 177, Folder 1251A)
    - Wetzel, James, 1990 Census Project, Trends in Labor Force Participation, Unemployment and Earnings, 909.301, Attachment File, 1993-1994 (Box 177, Folder 1252)
    - Whitehead, Tony Larry, Cultural and Class Variables Underlying Food Habits, 1978-1980 (Box 177, Folder 1253)
    - Whitehead, Tony Larry, Cultural and Class Variables Underlying Food Habits, 1978-1980 (Box 177, Folder 1253A)
    - Wildavsky, Aaron, The Battle of the Budget: An Inquiry Into Changes in American Politics, 1981-1988 (Box 177, Folder 1254)
    - Wildavsky, Aaron, The Battle of the Budget: An Inquiry Into Changes in American Politics, Attachment File, 1982 (Box 178, Folder 1255)
    - Wilensky, Harold, The Politics of Taxing and Spending, 1975-1980 (Box 178, Folder 1256)
    - Wilensky, Harold, The Politics of Taxing and Spending, 1975-1980 (Box 178, Folder 1256A)
    - Williams, Eddie N., Joint Center for Political Studies, Volume of Original Studies Comparing the Nature of Poverty and Welfare Policy in Western Europe, Canada and the United States, 998.931, 1989-1996 (Box 178, Folder 1257)
    - Williams, Eddie N., Joint Center for Political Studies, Volume of Original Studies Comparing the Nature of Poverty and Welfare Policy in Western Europe, Canada and the United States, 998.931, 1989-1996 (Box 178, Folder 1257A)
    - Williams, Eddie N., Joint Center for Political Studies, Volume of Original Studies Comparing the Nature of Poverty and Welfare Policy in Western Europe, Canada and the United States, 998.931, Attachment File, 1992 (Box 178, Folder 1258)
    - Williams, Linda Faye, Social Policy and the Politics of Race, 869.404, 1994-1997 (Box 178, Folder 1259)
    - Wilson, Bart J., Are Sticky Prices Really Possible in a Competative Market?, 989.505, 1995-1996 (Box 179, Folder 1260)
    - Wilson, Bart J., Are Sticky Prices Really Possible in a Competative Market?, 989.505, 1995-1996 (Box 179, Folder 1260A)
    - Wilson, William J. and Loic Wacquant, Support of the Costs of the American Delegation to the 1991 May 10-11 Working Conference on Poverty, Immigration and Urban Marginality in Advanced Societies, 998.953, 1990-1992 (Box 179, Folder 1261)
    - Wilson, William J. and Loic Wacquant, Support of the Costs of the American Delegation to the 1991 May 10-11 Working Conference on Poverty, Immigration and Urban Marginality in Advanced Societies, 998.953, Attachment File I (Box 179, Folder 1262)
    - Wilson, William J. and Loic Wacquant, Support of the Costs of the American Delegation to the 1991 May 10-11 Working Conference on Poverty, Immigration and Urban Marginality in Advanced Societies, 998.953, Attachment File II (Box 179, Folder 1263)
    - Winship, Christopher, Education, Mental Ability and Social Economic Success, 85-96-15, 1996-1998 (Box 179, Folder 1264)
    - Winship, Christopher, Education, Mental Ability and Social Economic Success, 85-96-15, 1996-1998 (Box 179, Folder 1264A)
    - Winship, Christopher and Sanders Konenman, The Analysis of the Bell Curve by Richard Herrnstein and Charles Murray, 979.503, 1994-1997 (Box 179, Folder 1265)
    - Winship, Christopher and Sanders Konenman, The Analysis of the Bell Curve by Richard Herrnstein and Charles Murray, 979.503, 1994-1997 (Box 179, Folder 1265A)
    - Winsten, Jay A., Presidential Grant, Improve Quality of Science News Reporting by Helping Journalists to Strengthen Their Understadning of Statstistics, 1984-1989 (Box 179, Folder 1266)
    - Wiseman, Michael, A Conference on State Welfare Innovations, 97-87-32, 1992-1997 (Box 180, Folder 1267)
    - Witte, John F., The Development and Politics of Federal Income Tax, 1980-1982 (Box 180, Folder 1268)
    - Wolfe, Alan, Middle Class Moralities, 979.409, 1994-1999 (Box 180, Folder 1269)
    - Wolfe, Alan, Middle Class Moralities, 979.409, 1994-1999 (Box 180, Folder 1269A)
    - Wolfe, Barbara, Earnings Inequality: The Rold of Fringe Benefits, 85-95-10, 1995-2003 (Box 180, Folder 1270)
    - Wolfe, Barbara, Earnings Inequality: The Rold of Fringe Benefits, 85-95-10, 1995-2003 (Box 180, Folder 1270A)
    - Yeaton, William H., Meta-Analytic Study of the Effectiveness of Non-Drug Approaches to the Control of Hypertension, 1987-1989 (Box 180, Folder 1271)
    - Yeaton, William H., Meta-Analytic Study of the Effectiveness of Non-Drug Approaches to the Control of Hypertension, 1987-1989 (Box 180, Folder 1271A)
    - Yeaton, William H., Meta-Analytic Study of the Effectiveness of Non-Drug Approaches to the Control of Hypertension, Attachment FIle, 1989 (Box 180, Folder 1272)
    - Yinger, John and Margery A. Turner, A Book Project Based Upon the 1988-1990 HUD (Housing and Urban Development) Study of Housing Discrimination, 1991-1996 (Box 181, Folder 1273)
    - Yinger, John and Margery A. Turner, A Book Project Based Upon the 1988-1990 HUD (Housing and Urban Development) Study of Housing Discrimination, 1991-1996 (Box 181, Folder 1273A)
    - Yinger, John and Margery A. Turner, A Book Project Based Upon the 1988-1990 HUD (Housing and Urban Development) Study of Housing Discrimination, Attachment File, 1991-1992 (Box 171, Folder 1274)
    - Young, H. Peyton, Presidential Grant, The Equitable Application of Public Resources, 1987-1991 (Box 181, Folder 1275)
    - Young, H. Peyton, Presidential Grant, The Equitable Application of Public Resources, Attachment File, 1989 (Box 181, Folder 1276)
    - Young, H. Peyton, A Book on Fair Division of Public Resources, 978.719, 1989-1994 (Box 181, Folder 1277)
    - Young, H. Peyton, A Book on Fair Division of Public Resources, 978.719, 1989-1994 (Box 181, Folder 1277A)
    - Young, H. Peyton, A Book on Fair Division of Public Resources, 978.719, Attachment File, 1991 (Box 182, Folder 1278)
    - Yuchtman-Yaar, Ephraim, Objective and Subjective Features of Israeli Labor Force: A Comparative Perspective, 1979-1982 (Box 182, Folder 1279)
    - Zablocki, Benjamin, Structural Consequences of Shift from Family Care to Group Care of Pre-Schoolers, 1974-1981 (Box 182, Folder 1280)
    - Zajonc, Robert B., Presidential Grant, A Book of Essays on the Polish Spring of 1989, Co-Edited With Janusz Grzelak and Written by the Social and Behavioral Scientists Who Took Part in Poland's Democratization, 988.927, 1990-1993 (Box 182, Folder 1281)
    - Zajonc, Robert B., Presidential Grant, A Book of Essays on the Polish Spring of 1989, Co-Edited With Janusz Grzelak and Written by the Social and Behavioral Scientists Who Took Part in Poland's Democratization, 988.927, 1990-1993 (Box 182, Folder 1281A)
    - Zajonc, Robert B., Presidential Grant, A Book of Essays on the Polish Spring of 1989, Co-Edited With Janusz Grzelak and Written by the Social and Behavioral Scientists Who Took Part in Poland's Democratization, 988.927, Attachment File, 1990-1993 (Box 182, Folder 1282)
    - Zajonc, Robert B., Presidential Grant, A Book of Essays on the Polish Spring of 1989, Co-Edited With Janusz Grzelak and Written by the Social and Behavioral Scientists Who Took Part in Poland's Democratization, 988.927, Attachment File, 1990-1993 (Box 182, Folder 1282A)
    - Zunz, Olivier, University of Virginia, International Working Group on the Middle Class of the Twenty-First Century, 97-97-07, 1997-1998 (Box 182, Folder 1283)
    - Zunz, Olivier, University of Virginia, International Working Group on the Middle Class of the Twenty-First Century, 97-97-07, Attachment File, 1995 (Box 182, Folder 1284)
  - Visiting Scholars, 1987-1990, 1999-2000; 4; 0.3 Cubic Feet
    - Visiting Scholars, 1987-1988 (Box 183, Folder 1285)
    - Visiting Scholars, 1987-1988 (Box 183, Folder 1285A)
    - Visiting Scholars, 1988-1989 (Box 183, Folder 1286)
    - Visiting Scholars, 1988-1989 (Box 183, Folder 1286A)
    - Visiting Scholars, 1989-1990 (Box 183, Folder 1287)
    - Visiting Scholars, 1989-1990 (Box 183, Folder 1287A)
    - Visiting Scholars, 1999-2000 (Box 183, Folder 1288)
    - Visiting Scholars, 1999-2000 (Box 183, Folder 1288A)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowship Program, 1976-1987; 5; 0.5 Cubic Feet
    - Postdoctoral Fellowship Program, 1980-1987 (Box 183, Folder 1289)
    - Applicants, 1985-1986 (Box 183, Folder 1290)
    - Forms and Form Letters, 1985-1987 (Box 183, Folder 1291)
    - Inter-Office Memos: Postdoctoral Fellows, 1976-1980 (Box 183, Folder 1292)
    - Memos to Selection Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 183, Folder 1293)
    - Roster of Applicants, 1986-1987 (Box 184, Folder 1294)
    - Selection Committee for Postdoctoral Fellowship Program, 1981-1987 (Box 184, Folder 1295)
    - Selection Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 184, Folder 1296)
    - Selection Committee, Correspondence, 1982 (Box 184, Folder 1297)
    - Selection Committee, Correspondence, 1982 (Box 184, Folder 1297A)
  - 1980 and 1990 Census, 1980-1995; 6; 4.4 Cubic Feet
    - 1980 Census, 1991 (Box 184, Folder 1298)
    - 1980 Census Blurbs, undated (Box 184, Folder 1299)
    - Annual Reports, 1992 (Box 184, Folder 1300)
    - Census Bureau, 1990-1991 (Box 184, Folder 1301)
    - Census Style Sheets, 1993 (Box 184, Folder 1302)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Russell Sage Foundation Grant (Box 184, Folder 1303)
    - NCR 1980 Census, January Conference, 1979-1980 (Box 184, Folder 1304)
    - NCR 1980 Census, September Conference (Box 184, Folder 1305)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Advisory Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 184, Folder 1306)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Authors' Addresses, undated (Box 184, Folder 1307)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Financial Status, 1982-1991 (Box 184, Folder 1308)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Ford Foundation, 805-0399, 1979-1980 (Box 184, Folder 1309)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Ford Foundation, 810-0671, 1981-1986 (Box 184, Folder 1310)
    - NCR 1980 Census, General, 1981 (Box 184, Folder 1311)
    - NCR 1980 Census, General, 1982 January-June (Box 185, Folder 1312)
    - NCR 1980 Census, General, 1982 July-December (Box 185, Folder 1313)
    - NCR 1980 Census, General, 1982-1984 (Box 185, Folder 1314)
    - NCR 1980 Census, General, 1983 (Box 185, Folder 1315)
    - NCR 1980 Census, General, 1984-1985 (Box 185, Folder 1316)
    - NCR 1980 Census, General, 1985-1988 (Box 185, Folder 1317)
    - NCR 1980 Census, General Support, Ford Foundation, 1983 (Box 185, Folder 1318)
    - NCR 1980 Census, General Support, Sloan Foundation, 1980-1981 (Box 186, Folder 1319)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Guidelines for Census, 1983 (Box 186, Folder 1320)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Monograph Committee, 1991 (Box 186, Folder 1321)
    - NCR 1980 Census, National Science Foundation I, SES 8214266, 1981-1985 (Box 186, Folder 1322)
    - NCR 1980 Census, National Science Foundation II, SES 8214266, 1982-1986 (Box 186, Folder 1323)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Reports to Trustees (Box 186, Folder 1324)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Sloan Foundation, Financial and Narrative Reports, 1981-1985 (Box 186, Folder 1325)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Sloan Foundation, Meeting With Census Officals, 1984-1986 (Box 186, Folder 1326)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Social Science Research Council, Meeting 1983 October 14-15 (Box 186, Folder 1327)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Social Science Research Council, Meeting 1984 January 5-6, 1983 (Box 186, Folder 1328)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Social Science Research Council Meeting, 1984 January 19-20, 1983-1984 (Box 186, Folder 1329)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Adams, John S., 1982-1986 (Box 186, Folder 1330)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Alonso, William and Paul Starr, 1982-1984 (Box 187, Folder 1331)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Bean, Frank, 1982-1984 (Box 187, Folder 1332)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Bean, Frank, 1982-1984 (Box 187, Folder 1332A)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Cain, Glen G., 1982-1987 (Box 187, Folder 1333)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Cain, Glen G., 1982-1987 (Box 187, Folder 1333A)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Farley, Reynolds and Walter R. Allen, 1981-1987 (Box 187, Folder 1334)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Farley, Reynolds and Walter R. Allen, 1981-1987 (Box 187, Folder 1334A)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Frey, William, 1983-1985 (Box 187, Folder 1335)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Fuguitt, Glen V., 1982-1986 (Box 187, Folder 1336)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Hernandez, Donald J. and David E. Meyers, 1982-1990 (Box 187, Folder 1337)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Jasso, Guillermina and Mark R. Rosenzweig, 1981-1989 (Box 187, Folder 1338)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Lieberson, Stanley, 1981-1987 (Box 187, Folder 1339)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Long, Larry, 1981-1986 (Box 187, Folder 1340)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Long, Larry, 1981-1986 (Box 187, Folder 1340A)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Siegel, Jacob S., 1982-1989 (Box 187, Folder 1341)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Snipp, C. Matthew, 1982-1988 (Box 188, Folder 1342)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Speare, Alden, Jr., 1982-1985 (Box 188, Folder 1343)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Sweet, James and Larry Bumpass, 1981-1985 (Box 188, Folder 1344)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Tienda, Marta, 1982-1985 (Box 188, Folder 1345)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Tienda, Marta, 1982-1985 (Box 188, Folder 1345A)
    - NCR 1980 Census, White, Michael J., 1981-1986 (Box 188, Folder 1346)
    - NCR 1980 Census, Xenos, Peter C., 1983-1989 (Box 188, Folder 1347)
    - Census Authors Meetings, Census Budget, 1992 (Box 189, Folder 1348)
    - Census Authors Meetings, Census Budget Projection, 1992 (Box 189, Folder 1349)
    - Census Authors Meetings, Census Conference Call, 1991 (Box 189, Folder 1350)
    - Census Authors Meetings, Census Bureau Payments, 1982 & 1991-1992 (Box 189, Folder 1351)
    - Census Authors Meetings, Census Bureau Report, 1994 (Box 189, Folder 1352)
    - Census Authors Meetings, Meeting, 1991 December 10 (Box 189, Folder 1353)
    - Census Authors Meetings, Meeting, 1993 September 30 (Box 189, Folder 1354)
    - Census Authors Meetings, Notes and News, 1993 (Box 189, Folder 1355)
    - Census Authors Meetings, Progam Activities Report, 1992 (Box 189, Folder 1356)
    - Census Authors Meetings, Undercount Project, 1991 (Box 189, Folder 1357)
    - 1990 Census Proposal, Budget Costs for 1990 Census, 1991 (Box 189, Folder 1358)
    - 1990 Census Proposal, Census Advisory Committee, Meeting Calendars, 1991 (Box 189, Folder 1359)
    - 1990 Census Proposal, Mailing List (Box 189, Folder 1360)
    - 1990 Census Proposal, 1990 Census, 1989-1994 (Box 189, Folder 1361)
    - 1990 Census Project, Addendum to Census Project, undated (Box 189, Folder 1362)
    - 1990 Census Project, Advisory Committee (Box 189, Folder 1363)
    - 1990 Census Project, Advisory Committee Memoranda, 1991-1993 (Box 189, Folder 1364)
    - 1990 Census Project, Advisory Committee Reactions (Box 189, Folder 1365)
    - 1990 Census Project, Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, Comptetitiveness Project (Box 189, Folder 1366)
    - 1990 Census Project, Author Conference, 1993 (Box 189, Folder 1367)
    - 1990 Census Project, Bell, David E., Howard Raiffa, and Amos Tversky (Box 189, Folder 1368)
    - 1990 Census Project, Board of Trustees, 1992 February 26 (Box 189, Folder 1369)
    - 1990 Census Project, Budget, 1996 (Box 189, Folder 1370)
    - 1990 Census Project, Bureau of Statistics, Norwood Janet, 1991 (Box 190, Folder 1371)
    - 1990 Census Project, Carnegie Corporation, Hamburg, David A., 1991 (Box 190, Folder 1372)
    - 1990 Census Project, Census Author Mailing List, 1991 (Box 190, Folder 1373)
    - 1990 Census Project, Census Master File for Monograph on Puerto Rico, 1992 (Box 190, Folder 1374)
    - 1990 Census Project, Census News File, 1991 (Box 190, Folder 1375)
    - 1990 Census Project, Census Popular Authors, 1991 (Box 190, Folder 1376)
    - 1990 Census Project, Census Proposals, 1989-1994 (Box 190, Folder 1377)
    - 1990 Census Project, Census Proposals, 1989-1994 (Box 190, Folder 1377A)
    - 1990 Census Project, Census Volume Proposals, 1991 (Box 190, Folder 1378)
    - 1990 Census Project, Census Public Use Microdata Samples (PUMS) Data, 1991-1993 (Box 190, Folder 1379)
    - 1990 Census Project, Census Schedule, undated (Box 190, Folder 1380)
    - 1990 Census Project, Census Titles, undated (Box 190, Folder 1381)
    - 1990 Census Project, Committee Members, undated (Box 190, Folder 1382)
    - 1990 Census Project, Common Information Material for All 1990 Census Project Awards, 1993-1995 (Box 190, Folder 1383)
    - 1990 Census Project, Common Information Material for All 1990 Census Project Awards, Attachment File I, 1991-1995 (Box 190, Folder 1384)
    - 1990 Census Project, Common Information Material for All 1990 Census Project Awards, Attachment File I, 1991-1995 (Box 190, Folder 1384A)
    - 1990 Census Project, Common Information Material for All 1990 Census Project Awards, Attachment File II, 1993-1995 (Box 191, Folder 1385)
    - 1990 Census Project, Council on Competitiveness (Box 191, Folder 1386)
    - 1990 Census Project, De Janosi, Peter, 1988-1990 (Box 191, Folder 1387)
    - 1990 Census Project, Department of Housing & Urban Development (HUD), Weicher, John, 1991 (Box 191, Folder 1388)
    - 1990 Census Project, Department of Labor, Ishikawa, Mamore, 1991 (Box 191, Folder 1389)
    - 1990 Census Project, Easterlin, Richard, University of Southern California, 1991 (Box 191, Folder 1390)
    - 1990 Census Project, Fannie Mae, 1991-1992 (Box 191, Folder 1391)
    - 1990 Census Project, Fannie Mae Mortgage, 1991-1992 (Box 191, Folder 1392)
    - 1990 Census Project, Federal National Mortgage Association, Fannie Mae, Hornburg, Steven, 1991-1993 (Box 191, Folder 1393)
    - 1990 Census Project, Financial Reports, 1992 (Box 191, Folder 1394)
    - 1990 Census Project, The Ford Foundation, Arnold, David and William Diaz, 1991-1992 (Box 191, Folder 1395)
    - 1990 Census Project, The Ford Foundation, Monograph on Puerto Rico, 910-1323-1, 1992-1996 (Box 191, Folder 1396)
    - 1990 Census Project, The Ford Foundation, Monograph on Puerto Rico, 910-1323-1, 1992-1996 (Box 191, Folder 1396A)
      Contains time sensitive material --- open in 2018
    - 1990 Census Project, The Ford Foundation, A Three Volume Analysis of the 1990 Census, 910-1323, 1991-1995 (Box 192, Folder 1397)
    - 1990 Census Project, Funding, 1991-1992 (Box 192, Folder 1398)
    - 1990 Census Project, List of Names, Potential Census Authors, 1991 (Box 192, Folder 1399)
    - 1990 Census Project, List of Names, Potential Census Authors, 1991 (Box 192, Folder 1399A)